♪
( door rattles )
( Kirito sighs )
( grunts )
SYSTEM CALL.
GENERATE LUMINOUS ELEMENT.
( both gasp )
Eugeo: WOW.
LOOK AT ALL THIS STUFF.
Kirito: HURRY. LET’S FIND
OUR SWORDS AND GET OUT OF HERE.
( Eugeo gasps ) THERE THEY ARE!
♪
Kirito: I CAN LEAVE THE ROOM
IF YOU TWO NEED A MINUTE.
( Eugeo laughs ) SORRY.
I DON’T GET IT.
I THOUGHT THE INTEGRITY KNIGHTS
WERE ENOUGH
TO STOP THE FORCES OF DARKNESS.
IS THE CHURCH BUILDING AN ARMY?
Kirito: IT’S NOT THAT.
IT’S THE OPPOSITE, IN FACT.
THE CHURCH BROUGHT ALL THIS HERE
TO MAKE SURE NO ONE BUILDS ONE.
Eugeo: WHAT WOULD
BE THE POINT OF THAT?
Kirito: SIMPLE. THE CHURCH
DOESN’T WANT PEOPLE
RISIN’ UP AGAINST IT,
OR, TO BE MORE SPECIFIC,
ADMINISTRATOR DOESN’T.
Eugeo: UM...
Kirito: COME ON.
LET’S GET OUT OF HERE.
TIME’S A-WASTIN’.
Eugeo: YEAH, RIGHT. I’M COMING.
MAYBE WE SHOULD TAKE SOME ARMOR.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Kirito: WE NEVER
FOUGHT IN IT BEFORE,
SO IT MIGHT SLOW US DOWN.
IT’S BETTER
IF WE STICK TO WHAT WE KNOW.
WE COULD USE A FRESH SET
OF CLOTHES, THOUGH.
( door creaks )
( Kirito gasps )
( both yell )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ PROUD OF MYSELF ♪
♪
Kirito: BURST ELEMENT!
( Deusolbert grunts )
Kirito: CHARGE HIM!
Deusolbert: FUTILE.
- Eugeo: KIRITO, YOU HIT?!
- ( Kirito groans )
( chuckles ) NO. I’M GOOD.
THAT WAS WAY TOO CLOSE.
( Eugeo sighs )
LET’S GO.
Deusolbert: SYSTEM CALL.
♪
Kirito: UH-OH. NOT GOOD.
THAT’S NO TYPICAL SPELL.
IT’S PERFECT WEAPON CONTROL.
Deusolbert: ENHANCE ARMAMENT.
( Eugeo winces )
Kirito: THAT BOW’S AWESOME!
HOLY HELL.
I WONDER WHAT IT WAS BEFORE.
Eugeo: WE HAVE BIGGER THINGS
TO WORRY ABOUT!
Deusolbert: I LAST BATHED
IN THE CONFLAGRATION BOW’S FIRE
TWO YEARS AGO.
NOW I SUMMON THE FIRE AGAIN
TO DEAL WITH YOU SINNERS.
YOU HAVE THE SKILLS
TO MATCH SIR ELDRIE,
BUT WHAT YOU DID TO HIM
IS UNFORGIVEABLE.
INSTEAD OF FIGHTING
LIKE KNIGHTS WITH HONOR,
YOU CORRUPTED HIS MIND
AND LED HIM ASTRAY
WITH THE DARK ARTS.
Kirito: WHAT?!
IT WAS NOTHING LIKE THAT!
Eugeo: YOU’RE WRONG, SIR KNIGHT!
ALL WE DID WAS REMIND HIM
OF HIS LIFE
BEFORE HE BECAME A KNIGHT!
Deusolbert: WHAT ARE
YOU BABBLING ABOUT?
WE KNIGHTS DO NOT HAVE A PAST.
WE HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
INTEGRITY KNIGHTS.
OUR EXISTENCE BEGINS WHEN WE
ARE SUMMONED FROM THE HEAVENS.
( Eugeo gasps )
Deusolbert: I SHOULD BURN
YOU CRIMINALS TO ASH,
BUT MY ORDERS ARE
TO CAPTURE YOU ALIVE.
UNFORTUNATELY, I HAVE UNLEASHED
THE CONFLAGRATION BOW.
NOW ONE OF YOUR ARMS
WILL MOST LIKELY BE INCINERATED.
( Eugeo gasps )
Kirito: THAT BOW’S
GONNA DO SERIOUS DAMAGE NOW.
Eugeo: ANY IDEAS?
Kirito: I GOT A FEELING
HE CAN’T RAPID-FIRE WITH THAT.
IF I’M LUCKY AND BLOCK
THE FIRST SHOT, YOU CHARGE HIM.
Eugeo: EH,
THAT’S NOT REASSURING.
- ( gasps )
- ( Kirito chuckles )
( Eugeo sighs )
I’M READY.
( winces )
♪
Kirito: SYSTEM CALL!
GENERATE CRYOGENIC ELEMENT!
DISCHARGE!
( woman vocalizing )
Deusolbert: FOOL!
( Kirito gasps )
( yelling )
( winces )
( yells )
- ( groans )
- Eugeo: KIRITO!
( Kirito gasps )
NOW’S YOUR CHANCE! GO GET HIM!
Deusolbert: HMM?
( Eugeo yells )
Deusolbert: DO NOT TOY WITH ME!
Eugeo: NOW WHAT?!
( panting )
Kirito: YOU HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOU’RE PUTTING
BEHIND YOUR STRIKES.
Eugeo: WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD PUT BEHIND MINE, THEN?
Kirito: THAT’S SOMETHING
YOU’RE GONNA HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT YOURSELF.
♪
Eugeo: THAT’S IT.
SHE’S ALL THAT MATTERS.
I’M HERE FOR HER,
AND NOTHING WILL STOP ME!
BLUE ROSE SWORD,
LEND ME YOUR POWER.
PLEASE, GIVE ME THE STRENGTH
TO KEEP GOING!
( roars )
( Deusolbert grunting )
♪
Eugeo: PLEASE.
YOU’RE COLD AND SHARP,
FORGED SINCE CREATION
BY FREEZING COLD BLIZZARDS
AT THE TOP OF THE END MOUNTAINS.
YOU CAN’T LET
THESE WEAK FLAMES...
MELT YOU NOW!
( yells )
( Deusolbert groans )
Eugeo: YOU’RE FINISHED.
( Deusolbert gasping )
( Eugeo yells )
( Deusolbert groans )
( groans )
( sword hums )
♪
( Eugeo gasps )
( Deusolbert gasping )
BOY, THAT FIRST SKILL YOU USED,
WHAT WAS IT?
Eugeo:
IT’S OF THE AINCRAD STYLE,
A TWO HIT STRIKE, VERTICAL ARC.
Deusolbert: A TWO-HIT STRIKE?
AND YOU...
WHAT WAS YOUR SKILL?
Eugeo: KIRITO, ARE YOU OKAY?
Kirito: YEAH, I’M GOOD.
I HEALED THE WORST BURNS MYSELF.
WHAT’S MY SKILL?
IT’S AINCRAD, TOO,
ONE OF THE DEFENSE SKILLS.
IT’S CALLED SPINNING SHIELD.
( Deusolbert sighs )
I THOUGHT I HAD SEEN IT ALL.
I’VE BEEN FROM ONE END
OF THIS REALM TO THE OTHER
AND BEYOND, AND YET THERE
ARE STYLES I’VE NEVER SEEN
AND SKILLS
I’VE NEVER ENCOUNTERED.
I CAN TELL THERE IS
MUCH DISCIPLINE IN YOU
AND YOU HAVE SPENT YEARS
OF TRAINING IN YOUR STYLE.
EARLIER, I ACCUSED YOU
OF USING THE DARK ARTS
TO CORRUPT SIR ELDRIE.
I KNOW NOW THAT I WAS MISTAKEN.
I WOULD BE HONORED
TO KNOW YOUR NAMES.
Eugeo: I AM EUGEO,
THE SWORDSMAN.
Kirito: KIRITO, THE SWORDSMAN.
( Deusolbert sighs )
ON THE 50th FLOOR,
IN THE GREAT HALL
OF GHOSTLY LIGHT,
INTEGRITY KNIGHTS WAIT,
SHOULD YOU PASS ME.
THEY WILL NOT TAKE YOU PRISONER.
THEY HAVE ORDERS TO EXTINGUISH
YOUR LIVES INSTEAD.
IF YOU CHARGE THEM HEAD-ON
LIKE YOU DID ME JUST NOW,
YOU WILL MOST CERTAINLY
MEET YOUR END.
Kirito: WHOA. HANG ON A SEC.
WHY TELL US?
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
( Deusolbert sighs )
I FAILED TO CARRY OUT
ADMINISTRATOR’S ORDER.
I SHALL BE STRIPPED
OF MY ARMOR AND DIVINE OBJECT,
THE PROOF OF MY KNIGHTHOOD.
THEN I SHALL BE
FROZEN FOR ETERNITY.
I DO NOT WISH TO SUFFER
THAT INDIGNITY.
THEREFORE...
I WANT YOU TO END MY LIFE.
( both gasp )
Deusolbert:
THERE IS NO NEED TO HESITATE.
AFTER ALL,
YOU DEFEATED ME FAIRLY
USING YOUR SPLENDID SKILLS.
BY THE WAY,
MY NAME IS
DEUSOLBERT SYNTHESIS SEVEN.
( Eugeo gasps )
♪
Eugeo: YOU’RE DEUSOLBERT?
Kirito: EUGEO.
Eugeo: YOU’RE THE ONE
WHO TOOK HER.
A FAIR BATTLE? DIGNITY?
YOU WANT TO DIE WITH HONOR...
DO YOU?
DO YOU?!
WHERE WAS YOUR HONOR WHEN YOU
CHAINED UP AN 11-YEAR-OLD GIRL?!
YOU TIED HER TO YOUR DRAGON
AND TOOK HER AWAY!
DYING WITH HONOR
IS TOO GOOD FOR YOU!
( gasps )
I’M RIGHT.
I AM. AREN’T I?
Kirito: YOU HEARD WHAT HE SAID.
HE’S NOT GONNA FIGHT BACK.
YOU DON’T KILL
A DEFENSELESS PERSON.
Eugeo: I KNOW, BUT...
HE CAME TO MY VILLAGE
AND TOOK ALICE!
♪
Kirito: YOU KNOW THE CHURCH
MESSES WITH THESE GUYS’S HEADS.
I DOUBT HE REMEMBERS BEING
IN RULID OR TAKING ALICE AWAY.
( Eugeo gasps )
Kirito: IT’S TRUE, AIN’T IT?
YOU DON’T REMEMBER.
Deusolbert:
IT IS AS YOUR COMPANION SAYS.
I AM A KNIGHT.
I PROTECT.
I WOULD NEVER KIDNAP A CHILD,
MUCH LESS CHAIN THEM
TO MY DRAGON.
IF I DID, I DO NOT REMEMBER.
Eugeo: WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IT HAPPENED EIGHT YEARS AGO!
Kirito: OLD MAN--
I MEAN, DEUSOLBERT.
EIGHT YEARS AGO,
YOU WERE GUARDING
THE BORDER OF NORTH NORLANGARTH.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT?
Deusolbert: I DO.
DISTRICT SEVEN
IN NORTH NORLANGARTH WAS MINE.
I USED TO PATROL
THE BORDERLANDS.
THAT IS, UNTIL EIGHT YEARS AGO.
FOR SOME REASON,
THE CHURCH REWARDED ME.
I RECEIVED THIS ARMOR
AND WAS GIVEN THE DUTY
TO GUARD THE CENTRAL CATHEDRAL.
Kirito: DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT
THE CHURCH REWARDED YOU FOR?
( Deusolbert sighing )
Kirito: I’LL TELL YOU
WHY YOU DON’T.
YOU WERE ON A MISSION
TO STEAL HIS FRIEND.
SHE’S CALLED
ALICE SYNTHESIS THIRTY NOW.
AS SOON AS YOU
BROUGHT HER BACK HERE,
ADMINISTRATOR REWARDED YOU,
ALL RIGHT.
SHE ALSO ERASED YOUR MEMORY
OF WHAT YOU DID,
’CAUSE SHE CAN’T
HAVE YOU REMEMBERING HER.
YOU TOLD US BEFORE THAT
INTEGRITY KNIGHTS HAVE NO PAST,
YOUR LIVES BEGIN WHEN YOU’RE
SUMMONED FROM HEAVEN,
BUT THAT’S A LIE.
THAT’S SOMETHING THE PONTIFEX
TELLS ALL THE KNIGHTS
RIGHT AFTER THEY COME TO,
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
TO HELP EXPLAIN WHY NONE OF YOU
CAN REMEMBER ANYTHING BEFORE
BECOMING AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT.
SHE DOESN’T WANT YOU TO HAVE
ANY MEMORIES, NOT EVEN ONE,
AND SHE DOESN’T STOP WITH
THE MEMORIES OF YOUR HUMAN LIFE.
SHE TAKES THE ONES YOU HAVE
OF OTHER KNIGHTS, TOO,
THE ONES YOU BROUGHT TO HER
TO GET TURNED.
IF A SINNER
YOU BROUGHT IN FOR JUDGMENT
SHOWED UP AS A KNIGHT
THE NEXT DAY
AND YOU REMEMBERED THEM,
THERE’D BE CHAOS.
Deusolbert:
BUT I WOULD REMEMBER.
I WOULD.
Kirito: LIKE I SAID,
ADMINISTRATOR
STOLE YOUR MEMORIES,
AND THEN SHE FORCED
ABSOLUTE LOYALTY ON YOU.
THEN SHE TURNED YOU
INTO A KNIGHT.
BUT YOU’RE HUMAN, JUST LIKE US.
Deusolbert: HUMAN?
AND HAVING
MY MEMORY MANIPULATED?
BY THE PONTIFEX?
IMPOSSIBLE. ABSURD.
NO, BOY.
YOU ARE THE ONE
WHO IS MISTAKEN HERE.
Kirito: LOOK,
TRY TO REMEMBER SOMETHING,
ANYTHING AT ALL.
I BET THERE’S AN IMAGE
OR A FEELING THERE,
SOMETHING SO PRECIOUS TO YOU,
NO ART CAN ERASE IT.
Deusolbert:
FROM THE TIME I FIRST DESCENDED,
I KEEP HAVING THE SAME DREAM,
A DELICATE HAND
SHAKING ME AWAKE
AND ON ONE FINGER
A SILVER RING.
AND WHEN I DO WAKE UP,
THERE’S NO ONE THERE.
Kirito: WHOEVER
THAT HAND BELONGS TO
IS SOMEONE SPECIAL TO YOU.
ADMINISTRATOR STOLE
YOUR MEMORY OF ’EM.
WHAT YOU DO NEXT IS UP TO YOU.
YOU CAN GO BACK TO ADMINISTRATOR
AND ACCEPT YOUR PUNISHMENT,
OR YOU CAN HEAL YOURSELF
AND COME AFTER US.
YOUR CALL.
♪
( Eugeo sighs )
Kirito: ALL THESE STAIRS,
HOW FAR UP ARE WE NOW?
Eugeo: THE NEXT FLOOR
IS THE 29th.
AT THE RATE WE’RE GOING,
WE’LL REACH THE 50th FLOOR
IN HALF AN HOUR.
SHOULD WE JUST CHARGE IN?
( Kirito sighs )
GOOD QUESTION.
MM?
Eugeo: YOU THINK OF EVERYTHING.
Kirito: AFTER SEEIN’
HOW THAT LAST DUDE FOUGHT,
I GOT A THEORY. COMBO ATTACKS
SEEM TO THROW THESE KNIGHTS OFF.
IT’S LIKE THEY NEVER
HAD TO DEAL WITH ’EM BEFORE.
IF IT’S ONE-ON-ONE
AND WE COULD GET UP CLOSE,
I THINK WE’D HAVE A CHANCE.
BUT THAT KNIGHT SAID
THERE’S A BUNCH UP THERE
AND THEY’RE READY FOR US.
THAT’S GONNA MAKE THINGS HARDER.
Eugeo: YOU’RE RIGHT.
PERHAPS WE SHOULD AVOID THEM,
FIND ANOTHER WAY UP.
Kirito: YEAH,
I DON’T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
CARDINAL SAID THESE STAIRS
WERE THE ONLY WAY UP,
SO WE’RE GONNA
HAVE TO DEAL WITH ’EM.
EVEN IF WE DID FIND
A WAY AROUND,
WE’D HAVE TO FACE ’EM
ON THE WAY BACK DOWN.
WE SHOULD DEAL
WITH THOSE KNIGHTS NOW.
OUR NEW SPECIAL SKILL
SHOULD HELP.
Eugeo: THAT’S RIGHT.
PERFECT WEAPON CONTROL.
Kirito: YUP. MAYBE IF WE
USE IT WHEN WE CHARGE IN,
WE CAN TAKE A BUNCH OUT
BEFORE THEY CAN REACT.
WITH ANY LUCK,
OUR FIRST STRIKE’LL GET ’EM ALL.
Eugeo: ACTUALLY,
WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT THAT.
I DON’T THINK I’LL BE MUCH HELP.
MY VERSION
OF PERFECT WEAPON CONTROL
ISN’T A DIRECT ATTACK LIKE
THAT INTEGRITY KNIGHT’S WAS.
Kirito: WHAT?! Y-YOU’RE KIDDING!
Eugeo: UH-UH.
NOT BASED ON THE COMMAND
CARDINAL WROTE FOR ME.
I MEAN, I GUESS, IN THE END,
IT’S MY FAULT FOR IMAGINING IT.
Kirito: WELL,
LET ME CHECK IT OUT
AND SEE WHAT’S UP WITH IT.
Eugeo: OKAY.
Kirito: YEAH, YOU’RE RIGHT.
IT MIGHT NOT BE QUICK ENOUGH
FOR A SURPRISE ATTACK.
STILL, IT SHOULD COME IN HANDY,
AS LONG AS YOU USE IT RIGHT.
PLUS, IT LOOKS
LIKE IT COMPLEMENTS
MY PERFECT CONTROL ART.
Eugeo: REALLY?
CAN I SEE WHAT YOURS IS LIKE?
Kirito: NAH. I DON’T
WANNA SPOIL THE SURPRISE.
( Eugeo chuckles )
LET’S GET GOING.
HUH?
♪
( girls gasp )
( Eugeo gasps )
( girls sigh )
Kirito: WE SEE YOU. COME OUT.
Eugeo: THEY’RE CHILDREN.
Singer: ♪ OH, EVERYTHING
TURNS TO ASH, TO ASH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ AND EVERYTHING
TURNS TO DUST, TO DUST ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ FORGET-ME-NOT ♪